The world's most dangerous secret lies between them.
The Gorge is a romance, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Scott Derrickson.
Two highly trained operatives grow close from a distance after being
sent to guard opposite sides of a mysterious gorge.
When an evil below emerges, they must work together to survive what lies within.
Levi, played by Miles Teller.
Drasa, played by Anya Taylor-Joy.
Bartholomew, played by Sigourney Weaver.
J.D., played by Ṣọpẹ́ Dìrísù.
Erikas, played by William Houston.
Black Ops Commander, played by Kobna Holdbrook-Smith.
The Gorge is a 2025 American science fiction romantic action horror film
directed by Scott Derrickson and written by Zach Dean.
The film stars Miles Teller, Anya Taylor-Joy, and Sigourney Weaver.
Its plot follows two elite snipers who are ordered to guard a
deep gorge without knowing what lies inside.
The Gorge was released by Apple TV+ on February 14, 2025.
It received a mixed reception from critics.
The film explores themes of canyon, fog, romance, tower, elite sniper.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.